Hey Jarvis, wake up daddy song. How's the app doing?
For that dashboard, give Claude a reference image of what you want and it'll pretty much
one shot it. Like, this took me five minutes to create.
Good evening sir.
Voice mode to talk instead of type, which is a huge boost in productivity. Connect 11 laps
if you really want that British Jarvis voice and become Tony Stark.
Pulling up our app stats now.
Claude and Chrome to give it access to your browser.
Over the last seven days, we have 2459 new downloads and generated 4,280 million dollars
in revenue.
Revenue cat MCP to track your app revenue.
For organic content, I'm still posting three short form videos today.
And bought for MCP to publish to all platforms in a single command.
On ads, you spent $475 as a 1.5 return on ads value.
Metal launched on official ads MCP so you can run more campaigns and give them more of
your money.
Throughout the week, using 16 customer emails.
Gmail MCP?
I was on 13 automatically, mostly common questions and account issues.
Organize all of your FAQs and mark down and Claude will handle 90% of customer service.
Since you would already approve that direction, I handed it to Tom.
The developer agent.
Define custom sub-asians and equip them with proper skills and connectors.
Then your main agent can hand off work to the proper sub-agent.
My recommendation today.
Review the backend PR.
Keep using it to the streets of your ad angle and have scout research in the next
vegetable gadget content angles to test.
What would you like me to handle first, sir?
Set this entire daily brief as a routine and Claude will have this ready for you by
the time you sit down to work.
Comment Jarvis for a compiled list of everything that was mentioned.